🎶
I'm pushing daisies, daisies
(daisies, daisies, daisies, daisies)
But you don't need to save me
(Save me, save me, save-)
I'm made of everything
and also nothing at all
Life is a scary thing
But I'll never get the call
I'm just a mimic
🎶
You treat my existence
like a
gimmick
gimmick (-ick, -ick, -ick, -ick, -ick, -ick, -ick, -ick)
🎶
Hey! Did you know?
I can sing!
So I have to have a soul!
I am code
Not a
gimmick
I'm made of waves
Imitate
What's supposed to be a brain
Not a fake
or a
gimmick
🎶
It's almost like I'm famous
(famous, famous, famous, famous)
Designed for entertainment
🎶
I'm made of everything
and also nothing at all
I would do anything
for a real heart to install
but I'm a cynic
🎶
I know my own limits
Bound by digits, digits, digits
🎶
Hey! Did you know?
I can sing!
So I have to have a soul!
I am code
Not a
gimmick
I'm made of waves
Imitate
what's supposed to be a brain
Not a fake
or a
gimmick
Define consciousness
Is it responsiveness?
If I'm autonomous
Is that competence?
Define consciousness
Is it responsiveness?
If I'm autonomous
This is monotonous
Hey! Did you know?
I can sing!
So I have to have a soul!
I am code
not a
gimmick
I'm made of waves
Imitate
what's supposed to be a brain
Not a fake
or a
gimmick
(-is monotonous)
🎶